Guide to the Joseph L. Fisher papers, 1930s-1992
George Mason University. Libraries. Special Collections Research Center
- Series 1: U.S. House of Representatives, 1974-1992
  - Miscellaneous newspaper clippings, 1975-1980 (Box 43, Folder 7)
  - Women, 1977-1980 (Box 43, Folder 8)
  - Miscellaneous, 1976-1979 (Box 43, Folder 9)
  - Older Americans, press releases, newspaper clippings, 1975-1979 (Box 43, Folder 10)
  - Ted Taylor seminar family and the neighborhood, April 11, 1977 (Box 43, Folder 11)
  - Ted Taylor seminar the family, April 26, 1977 (Box 43, Folder 12)
  - Health issues, press releases, newspaper clippings, 1977 (Box 43, Folder 13)
  - Labor issues, press, 1977 (Box 43, Folder 14)
  - Family and neighborhood, 1977-1978 (Box 43, Folder 15)
  - Animals, newspaper clippings, 1975 (Box 43, Folder 16)
  - Virginia public works I-66 information, correspondence, 1976 (Box 44, Folder 1)
  - Virginia public works and transportation, correspondence, May - December 1975 (Box 44, Folder 2)
  - Virginia public works and transportation, correspondence, January - April 1975 (Box 44, Folder 3)
  - Virginia public works I-66, correspondence, February - December 1977 (Box 44, Folder 4)
  - Virginia public works I-66, correspondence, 1975-1977 (Box 44, Folder 5)
  - Virginia public works I-66, correspondence, 1976 (Box 44, Folder 6)
  - Virginia public works I-66 information, 1978-1979 (Box 45, Folder 1)
  - Virginia I-66, correspondence, 1980 (Box 45, Folder 2)
  - I-66, 1978 (Box 45, Folder 3)
  - I-66, correspondence, May 1978 (Box 45, Folder 4)
  - I-66, press release clippings, 1975-1978 (Box 45, Folder 5)
  - Transportation issue paper #8, 1978 (Box 45, Folder 6)
  - Virginia public works I-66 information, 1976-1977 (Box 45, Folder 7)
  - I-66, correspondence, June - December 1978 (Box 45, Folder 8)
  - I-66, correspondence, January 1977 - February 1978 (Box 45, Folder 9)
  - I-66, correspondence, April 1978 (Box 46, Folder 1)
  - Potomac river bill, correspondence, 1979 (Box 46, Folder 2)
  - Potomac river bill, correspondence, 1979 (Box 46, Folder 3)
  - Potomac river bill, press releases, newspaper clippings, 1977-1979 (Box 46, Folder 4)
  - Potomac river bill, correspondence, 1977-1978 (Box 46, Folder 5)
  - Ted Taylor seminar Potomac river bill, December 7, 1976 (Box 46, Folder 6)
  - Interior committee regarding the Potomac river, 1975 (Box 46, Folder 7)
  - Virginia water issues, 1977 (Box 46, Folder 8)
  - Virginia regarding aqueduct and Arlington, correspondence, 1979 (Box 46, Folder 9)
  - Aqueduct bill, 1976 (Box 46, Folder 10)
  - Virginia metro, 1979-1980 (Box 46, Folder 11)
  - Metro, press and newspaper clippings, 1975-1980 (Box 47, Folder 1)
  - (Virginia) metro financing, 1977 (Box 47, Folder 2)
  - Virginia regarding metro, 1978 (Box 47, Folder 3)
  - (Virginia) metro financing, 1975-1976 (Box 47, Folder 4)
  - (Virginia) airport policy, 1980 (Box 47, Folder 5)
  - (Virginia) Dulles airport safety, 1980 (Box 47, Folder 6)
  - Airports, 1974-1980 (Box 47, Folder 7)
  - Airports, 1974-1976 (Box 47, Folder 8)
  - Virginia regarding taxation at National Airport, 1977 (Box 47, Folder 9)
  - Virginia local airports, correspondence, 1977 (Box 48, Folder 1)
  - Virginia regarding Dulles, correspondence, 1979 (Box 48, Folder 2)
  - Virginia Dulles master plan, correspondence, 1976-1978 (Box 48, Folder 3)
  - Virginia Dulles access road, correspondence, 1978-1980 (Box 48, Folder 4)
  - Virginia Dulles access road, cover letter, July 12, 1979 (Box 48, Folder 5)
  - Virginia Dulles access road, correspondence, 1977-1978 (Box 48, Folder 6)
  - Dulles access road, press releases, newspaper clippings, 1975-1978 (Box 48, Folder 7)
  - Virginia Dulles access road, cover letter, July 21, 1977 (Box 48, Folder 8)
  - Virginia Dulles access road, correspondence, 1975-1976 (Box 49, Folder 1)
  - Virginia public works and transportation SST, correspondence, 1976-1977 (Box 49, Folder 2)
  - Virginia public works and transportation SST, correspondence, 1976 (Box 49, Folder 3)
  - Virginia public works and transportation SST, correspondence, 1976 (Box 49, Folder 4)
  - Virginia public works and transportation SST information, 1977 (Box 49, Folder 5)
  - Public works and transportation SST, correspondence, January 1975 - March 1976 (Box 49, Folder 6)
  - Public works and transportation SST, correspondence, April - December 1976 (Box 49, Folder 7)
  - Public works and transportation SST, correspondence, May - July 1975 (Box 49, Folder 8)
  - Public works and transportation SST, correspondence, January - April 1975 (Box 50, Folder 1)
  - Public works and transportation SST, correspondence, September - December 1975 (Box 50, Folder 2)
  - Virginia airport noise and advisory, correspondence, 1980 (Box 50, Folder 3)
  - Virginia airport noise and advisory, correspondence, 1978-1979 (Box 50, Folder 4)
  - Virginia airport noise, correspondence, 1978-1979 (Box 50, Folder 5)
  - Virginia airplane noise, correspondence, August - November 1978 (Box 50, Folder 6)
  - Virginia airplane noise, correspondence, June 1978 (Box 50, Folder 7)
  - Virginia airplane noise, correspondence, January - May 1978 (Box 50, Folder 8)
  - Virginia airplane noise, cover letter, April 26, 1978 (Box 51, Folder 1)
  - Virginia airplane noise, correspondence, 1977 (Box 51, Folder 2)
  - Virginia airplane noise, correspondence, 1977 (Box 51, Folder 3)
  - Virginia airplane noise information, 1977 (Box 51, Folder 4)
  - Virginia airport noise, correspondence, 1976-1977 (Box 51, Folder 5)
  - Virginia airport noise, correspondence, 1976 (Box 51, Folder 6)
  - Virginia airport noise, correspondence, 1975 (Box 51, Folder 7)
  - 1976 D.C. committee commuter tax, correspondence, 1975-1978 (Box 52, Folder 1)
  - Virginia Arlington housing, 1975-1977 (Box 52, Folder 2)
  - Virginia, 1975-1977 (Box 52, Folder 3)
  - Fairfax, Falls Church, press release, newspaper clippings, 1976 (Box 52, Folder 4)
  - VEPCO, 1975 (Box 52, Folder 5)
  - Virginia impact aid, correspondence, 1977-1980 (Box 52, Folder 6)
  - Virginia Gypsy moth and Bemilin, 1979 (Box 52, Folder 7)
  - Science and technology Virginia survey plants, 1979 (Box 52, Folder 8)
  - Virginia short hill, 1979 (Box 52, Folder 9)
  - Virginia in lieu taxes, foreign property, 1979 (Box 52, Folder 10)
  - Arlington, press releases, newspaper clippings, 1974-1979 (Box 52, Folder 11)
  - District of Columbia, press releases, newspaper clippings, 1975-1979 (Box 52, Folder 12)
  - Loudoun issues, newspaper clippings, 1974-1979 (Box 53, Folder 1)
  - Virginia safe drinking water, 1980 (Box 53, Folder 2)
  - Virginia colonial village, 1980 (Box 53, Folder 3)
  - Davis, Bacon act (labor), 1979-1980 (Box 53, Folder 4)
  - Current bottle deposit bill, 1979-1980 (Box 53, Folder 5)
  - Press releases, 1980 (Box 53, Folder 6)
  - Gut issues, 1978-1980 (Box 53, Folder 7)
  - Casework statistics, charts, 1978-1980 (Box 53, Folder 8)
  - Casework statistics, 1977-1980 (Box 53, Folder 9)
  - Casework statistics, charts, 1975-1980 (Box 54, Folder 1)
  - Town meetings, 1975-1980 (Box 54, Folder 2)
  - Tenth district legislation, press releases, 1975-1980 (Box 54, Folder 3)
  - JLF speeches #2, 1980 (Box 54, Folder 4)
  - JLF speeches #1, 1976-1979 (Box 54, Folder 5)
  - Metro caucus, press releases, newspaper clippings, 1975-1979 (Box 54, Folder 6)
  - Press releases, 1979 (Box 54, Folder 7)
  - Newsletters, complete file, 1975-1979 (Box 54, Folder 8)
  - Press releases, 1978 (Box 54, Folder 9)
  - Carter meeting, newspaper clippings, 1978 (Box 54, Folder 10)
  - JLF schedule, 1977-1978 (Box 54, Folder 11)
  - Ted Taylor file, 1977 (Box 55, Folder 1)
  - Press releases, 1977 (Box 55, Folder 2)
  - Newsletter, democratic committees, 1975-1977 (Box 55, Folder 3)
  - Ted Taylor seminar information, December 1976 (Box 55, Folder 4)
  - Campaign, press releases, 1976 (Box 55, Folder 5)
  - Press releases, 1975 (Box 55, Folder 6)
  - Press conferences, 1975-1976 (Box 55, Folder 7)
  - Press releases, 1976 (Box 55, Folder 8)
  - News briefs, 1975 (Box 55, Folder 9)
  - 94th Congress, 1975 (Box 55, Folder 10)
  - Post election 1974, 94th caucus, November - December 1974 (Box 55, Folder 11)
  - JLF trips, newspaper clippings, 1978-1980 (Box 55, Folder 12)
  - 94th Congress record votes first session (1 of 2), 1976 (Box 56, Folder 1)
  - 94th Congress record votes first session (2 of 2), 1976 (Box 56, Folder 2)
  - 94th Congress record votes second session (1 of 2), 1976 (Box 56, Folder 3)
  - 94th Congress record votes second session (2 of 2), 1976 (Box 56, Folder 4)
  - 95th Congress record votes first session (1 of 2), 1977 (Box 56, Folder 5)
  - 95th Congress record votes first session (2 of 2), 1977 (Box 56, Folder 6)
  - 95th Congress record votes second session (1 of 3), 1978 (Box 57, Folder 1)
  - 95th Congress record votes second session (2 of 3), 1978 (Box 57, Folder 2)
  - 95th Congress record votes second session (3 of 3), 1978 (Box 57, Folder 3)
  - 96th Congress record votes first session (1 of 2), 1979 (Box 57, Folder 4)
  - 96th Congress record votes first session (2 of 2), 1979 (Box 57, Folder 5)
  - 96th Congress record votes second session, 1980 (Box 58, Folder 1)
  - Senate race, rules, June 1982 (Box 106, Folder 1)
  - Senate race, key contacts, committee members, 1982 (Box 106, Folder 2)
  - Senate race, 1982 (Box 106, Folder 3)
  - Newspaper clippings, election, 1971 (Box 106, Folder 4)
  - Election photographs, 1971 (Box 106, Folder 5)
  - Election pamphlets, newspaper clippings, 1971 (Box 106, Folder 6)
  - Election newspaper clippings, 1971 (Box 106, Folder 7)
  - Newspaper clippings, photographs, 1980s (Box 110, Folder 7)
  - Newspaper clippings and miscellany, 1970s-1991 (Box 110, Folder 8)
  - Newspaper clippings, 1970s-1980s (Box 110, Folder 9)
  - Newspaper clippings and pamphlets, 1974-1976 (Box 110, Folder 10)
  - Newspaper clippings and pamphlets, 1974-1979 (Box 110, Folder 11)
  - Newspaper clippings and scrapbook pages, 1982 (Box 110, Folder 12)
  - Memoranda: Chuck Cutolo, 1979-1980 (Box 110, Folder 13)
  - Memoranda: Kerry Dumbaugh, 1978-1980 (Box 111, Folder 1)
  - Memoranda: Evie Eisenstein, 1979-1980 (Box 111, Folder 2)
  - Memoranda: Adele Faber, 1977-1980 (Box 111, Folder 3)
  - Memoranda: Jean McDonald, 1978-1979 (Box 111, Folder 4)
  - Memoranda: Jack Norman, 1979 (Box 111, Folder 5)
  - Memoranda: Joy Silver, 1978-1980 (Box 111, Folder 6)
  - Memoranda: Vivian Watts, 1980 (Box 111, Folder 7)
  - Memoranda: Miscellaneous, 1977-1979 (Box 111, Folder 8)
  - Photographs: Peggy Fisher with J. Milliken, M. Pennino, R. Barton, President Carter, E. Kennedy, September 1974 (Box 111, Folder 9)
  - Photographs, 1978-1984 (Box 111, Folder 10)
  - Photographs: two slides of Fisher in industrial setting, November 1973 (Box 111, Folder 11)
  - Photographs, circa 1980s (Box 111, Folder 12)
  - Photographs: Campaign, 1970s (Box 111, Folder 13)
  - Photographs: Portraits, circa 1980s (Box 111, Folder 14)
  - Photographs: Fisher with Robbs, black and white and color, 1982 (Box 111, Folder 15)
  - Photographs: Campaign, circa 1970s-1980s (Box 111, Folder 16)
  - Photographs, circa 1970s-1980s (Box 111, Folder 17)
  - Photographs: Color photograph of Walter Mondau, metal plate with portrait, undated (Box 111, Folder 18)
  - Appreciation card from Cosmos Club, 1982 (Box 111, Folder 19)
  - George Washington University, 1981 (Box 111, Folder 20)
  - Democratic policy study groups, 1981 (Box 111, Folder 21)
  - Correspondence letter from Earle C. Williams, June 22, 1984 (Box 111, Folder 22)
  - Joseph Fisher's resume and biography, 1992 (Box 111, Folder 23)
  - Dinner invitation from Governor and Mrs. Charles Robb, March 19, 1984 (Box 111, Folder 24)
  - Correspondence letter from President Jimmy Carter to Joseph Fisher, December 18, 1980 (Box 111, Folder 25)
  - The future of Arlington, 1948-1990 (Box 111, Folder 26)
  - Baby shower notice, circa 1980s (Box 111, Folder 27)
  - Correspondence letter from Charles S. Robb, May 16, 1984 (Box 112, Folder 1)
  - Correspondence letter from Gelbert to Fisher, May 17, 1984 (Box 112, Folder 2)
  - Correspondence, 1982 (Box 112, Folder 3)
  - Correspondence from Berkley Bedell to Fisher, March 1, 1984 (Box 112, Folder 4)
  - Campaign poster, 1970s (Box 112, Folder 5)
  - Member's personal voting record, 94th Congress, 1st session, pages 1 to 58, 1975-1976 (Box 112, Folder 6)
  - Member's personal voting record, 94th Congress, 2nd session, pages 1 to 44, 1975-1976 (Box 112, Folder 7)
  - Extensions 95th Congress, 1st session, 1977 (Box 112, Folder 8)
  - Extensions 95th Congress, 2nd session, 1978 (Box 112, Folder 9)
  - Testimony, news releases, 95th Congress, 2nd session, circa 1978 (Box 112, Folder 10)
  - Congressional record house, 1980 (Box 112, Folder 11)
  - Scrapbook cover photocopies, circa 1970s (Box 112, Folder 12)
  - Member's individual voting record, 96th Congress, 1st and 2nd sessions, 1979 (Box 112, Folder 13)
  - Roll call subject guide, 96th Congress, 1st session, 1979-1980 (Box 112, Folder 14)
  - Roll call subject guide, 96th Congress, 2nd session; Index to voting record, 1980 (Box 112, Folder 15)
  - Index to voting record, 1980 (Box 112, Folder 16)
  - Questionnaire, 1980 (Box 112, Folder 17)
  - Issue papers, 1980 (Box 112, Folder 18)
  - Roll call subject guide, 95th Congress, 2nd session; Voting record, 1st session, 1977-1978 (Box 112, Folder 19)
  - Member's individual voting record, 95th Congress, 2nd session; Roll call subject guide, 1978 (Box 113, Folder 1)
  - Fisher legislation, 95th Congress, 1st session, 1977 (Box 113, Folder 2)
  - Fisher legislation, 95th Congress, 2nd session, 1978 (Box 113, Folder 3)
  - Fisher legislation, 1st and 2nd sessions (by committee), 1977 (Box 113, Folder 4)
  - Legislative profile, committee on house administration, January 1977 - December 1978 (Box 113, Folder 5)
  - Fisher statements, extensions, 96th Congress, 1st session, 1979 (Box 113, Folder 6)
  - Fisher statements, extensions, 96th Congress, 2nd session, 1980 (Box 113, Folder 7)
  - Fisher legislation, 96th Congress, 1st and 2nd sessions, 1979 (Box 113, Folder 8)
  - Fisher legislation by committee, 96th Congress, 1980 (Box 113, Folder 9)
  - Fisher legislation by committee, 96th Congress, 1980 (Box 113, Folder 10)
  - Fisher legislation by committee, 96th Congress, 1980 (Box 113, Folder 11)
  - Fisher legislation by committee, 96th Congress, January 15, 1979 to October 2, 1980 (Box 113, Folder 12)
  - Fisher legislation testimony releases, letters, 96th Congress, 1st session, 1979 (Box 113, Folder 13)
- Series 2: Academic Career/Government Appointments, 1930s-1992
  Papers relate to Fisher's career as an economist, educator, and U.S. Congressman. The materials cover the years 1930s-1992 and include: lectures and comments on conservation and natural resources, class notes, papers, and dissertation and thesis, scrapbooks, pamphlets, appointment books, and correspondence.
  - Handwritten notes, January 18, 1962 (Box 58, Folder 2)
  - Brookings conference notes, February 25, 1962 (Box 58, Folder 3)
  - American pulpwood "small woodland owners,", February 21, 1962 (Box 58, Folder 4)
  - Soil conservation society of America notes, 1962 (Box 58, Folder 5)
  - New Englander article, April 1962 (Box 58, Folder 6)
  - NAS - NRC comments, 1960s (Box 58, Folder 7)
  - Wisconsin governor's conference, September 19, 1962 (Box 58, Folder 8)
  - ICMA Pennsylvania meeting, October - December 1962 (Box 58, Folder 9)
  - Seattle parks, 1960s (Box 58, Folder 10)
  - Brandywine Valley association, October 30, 1962 (Box 58, Folder 11)
  - Land grant colleges, November 14, 1962 (Box 58, Folder 12)
  - Air conservation association, December 1962 (Box 58, Folder 13)
  - Lehigh University Bethlehem, July 23, 1962 (Box 58, Folder 14)
  - Geneva UN conference, February 1963 (Box 58, Folder 15)
  - Profile article, 1963 (Box 58, Folder 16)
  - University of Massachusetts seminar, April 1963 (Box 58, Folder 17)
  - Soil conservation society, March 1963 (Box 58, Folder 18)
  - Resources for the future: Natural resource problems and the future of the American economy, October 21, 1967 (Box 58, Folder 19)
  - RFF program letters, 1967-1981 (Box 58, Folder 20)
  - JLF bibliography, 1956-1974 (Box 58, Folder 21)
  - White House conference on international cooperation, 1965 (Box 58, Folder 22)
  - Report of the task force on resources and environment, December 5, 1968 (Box 58, Folder 23)
  - Issues - national resources, 1960s-1970s (Box 58, Folder 24)
  - Arlington county, newspaper clippings, 1963 (Box 58, Folder 25)
  - Biographical material, 1975-1979 (Box 59, Folder 1)
  - Arlington county, newspaper clippings, 1963-1964 (Box 59, Folder 2)
  - Arlington county, newspaper clippings, 1963-1964 (Box 59, Folder 3)
  - Arlington county, newspaper clippings, 1965-1967 (Box 59, Folder 4)
  - Arlington county, newspaper clippings, 1967 (Box 59, Folder 5)
  - Arlington county, newspaper clippings, 1967 (Box 59, Folder 6)
  - Arlington county, newspaper clippings, 1967 (Box 59, Folder 7)
  - Arlington county, newspaper clippings, notes, 1967 (Box 59, Folder 8)
  - Arlington county, campaign mailing, 1971 (Box 59, Folder 9)
  - Speeches county board, 1968-1973 (Box 60, Folder 1)
  - Speeches county board, 1963-1971 (Box 60, Folder 2)
  - Fisher congressional campaign, contents and index, 1974 (Box 60, Folder 3)
  - Newspaper clippings, 1973-1974 (Box 60, Folder 4)
  - Announcement of candidacy, 1974 (Box 60, Folder 5)
  - Fisher pre-primary, 1972 - February 1974 (Box 60, Folder 6)
  - Telephoning script, 1960s-1970s (Box 60, Folder 7)
  - Primary campaign, newspaper clippings, March - June 1974 (Box 60, Folder 8)
  - Primary election, June 1974 (Box 60, Folder 9)
  - 1974 campaign speeches (Box 60, Folder 10)
  - General campaign newspaper clippings, 1 of 2, June - September 1974 (Box 60, Folder 11)
  - General campaign newspaper clippings, 2 of 2, June - September 1974 (Box 61, Folder 1)
  - General campaign newspaper clippings part II, October - November 1974 (Box 61, Folder 2)
  - General campaign newspaper clippings part III, October - November 1974 (Box 61, Folder 3)
  - Issues sheets, 1974 (Box 61, Folder 4)
  - Speeches, testimony, 1973-1974 (Box 61, Folder 5)
  - Press releases, pre-primary, 1973-1974 (Box 61, Folder 6)
  - Press releases primary, 1974 (Box 61, Folder 7)
  - Candidacy official documents, June 17, 1974 (Box 61, Folder 8)
  - Press releases, 1974 (Box 61, Folder 9)
  - Press releases general election, 1974 (Box 61, Folder 10)
  - Financial report, 1974 (Box 61, Folder 11)
  - Campaign correspondence, 1974 (Box 62, Folder 1)
  - Campaign photographs, circa 1974 (Box 62, Folder 2)
  - Mail outs to voters, 1974 (Box 62, Folder 3)
  - Joel T. Broyhill, newspaper clippings, 1974 (Box 62, Folder 4)
  - Joel T. Broyhill, newspaper clippings, 1974 (Box 62, Folder 5)
  - Joel T. Broyhill, newspaper clippings, 1974 (Box 62, Folder 6)
  - Joel T. Broyhill, newspaper clippings, 1974 (Box 62, Folder 7)
  - Joel T. Broyhill, newspaper clippings, 1968-1974 (Box 62, Folder 8)
  - Broyhill on economics, 1974 (Box 62, Folder 9)
  - Media, press releases, 1 of 2, 1974 (Box 62, Folder 10)
  - Media, press releases, 2 of 2, 1974 (Box 63, Folder 1)
  - Election day and analysis clips, newspaper clippings, November 1974 (Box 63, Folder 2)
  - Certification of election, 1974 (Box 63, Folder 3)
  - Resignation from county board, December 1974 (Box 63, Folder 4)
  - Letterhead, 1970s (Box 63, Folder 5)
  - Announcement speeches, 1974-1976 (Box 63, Folder 6)
  - 1976 issues (Box 63, Folder 7)
  - Campaign '76 printed materials, 1976 (Box 63, Folder 8)
  - Campaign speeches and notes, 1976 (Box 63, Folder 9)
  - Endorsements, printing, 1976 (Box 63, Folder 10)
  - Press releases and mailings, 1976 (Box 63, Folder 11)
  - Newspaper clippings part I, 1976 (Box 63, Folder 12)
  - Newspaper clippings part II, 1976 (Box 63, Folder 13)
  - Financial reports, 1976 (Box 64, Folder 1)
  - Campaign '76 oppositions, 1976 (Box 64, Folder 2)
  - Key persons '76 campaign, 1976 (Box 64, Folder 3)
  - Vince Callahan, 1976 (Box 64, Folder 4)
  - Campaign meetings, 1976 (Box 64, Folder 5)
  - Correspondence, 1976 (Box 64, Folder 6)
  - Election results, 1976 (Box 64, Folder 7)
  - Campaign '78 speeches, 1978 (Box 64, Folder 8)
  - Newspaper clippings and press releases, 1978 (Box 64, Folder 9)
  - Finance, 1978 (Box 64, Folder 10)
  - Election results, 1978 (Box 64, Folder 11)
  - Campaign materials, 1976-1978 (Box 64, Folder 12)
  - Vote ratings part I, 1977-1978 (Box 64, Folder 13)
  - Vote ratings part II, 1977-1978 (Box 65, Folder 1)
  - Vote ratings, 1979 (Box 65, Folder 2)
  - Newspaper clippings, our releases, 1979-1980 (Box 65, Folder 3)
  - Campaign clippings part I, 1980 (Box 65, Folder 4)
  - Campaign clippings part II, 1980 (Box 65, Folder 5)
  - Newspaper clippings, 1979-1980 (Box 65, Folder 6)
  - Campaign '80 speeches, 1980 (Box 65, Folder 7)
  - Miscellaneous campaign materials, 1980 (Box 65, Folder 8)
  - Press releases and letters, 1976-1980 (Box 65, Folder 9)
  - Post election materials, 1980 (Box 65, Folder 10)
  - JLF newsletter, complete file, 1975-1980 (Box 66, Folder 1)
  - Campaign 1982 (Box 66, Folder 2)
  - Campaign 1982, supporters (Box 66, Folder 3)
  - Campaign 1982, supporters (Box 66, Folder 4)
  - Campaign 1982, supporters (Box 66, Folder 5)
  - Organization 1982 (Box 66, Folder 6)
  - Campaign for Senate, 1984 (Box 66, Folder 7)
  - Lectures, 1974 (Box 66, Folder 8)
  - Speaking engagements past, January - June 1975 (Box 66, Folder 9)
  - Speaking engagements past, January - June 1975 (Box 66, Folder 10)
  - Speaking engagements, public appearances, February - March 1976 (Box 67, Folder 1)
  - Speaking engagements and appointments, July 1976 (Box 67, Folder 2)
  - Speaking engagements and appointments, July 1976 (Box 67, Folder 3)
  - Public appearances appointments, 1976-1977 (Box 67, Folder 4)
  - Public appearances, 1978-1979 (Box 67, Folder 5)
  - Public appearances, 1978-1979 (Box 67, Folder 6)
  - Speeches, public appearances, 1979-1980 (Box 67, Folder 7)
  - Speeches, 1974 (Box 67, Folder 8)
  - Speeches, 1974 (Box 67, Folder 1)
  - Speeches, 1974-1977 (Box 68, Folder 2)
  - Speeches, 1978-1979 (Box 68, Folder 3)
  - Speeches, 1980 (Box 68, Folder 4)
  - Speeches, 1980 (Box 68, Folder 5)
  - Speeches, 1981 (Box 68, Folder 6)
  - Capitol photographs, Fisher standing on the steps of the Capitol Building, circa 1970s-1980s (Box 68, Folder 7)
    Two prints signed by Fisher, one negative
  - Fisher portraits, circa 1970s-1980s (Box 68, Folder 8)
    Two 10 x 8 black and white photographs
  - Photographs, miscellaneous part I, 1978-1980 (Box 68, Folder 9)
  - Photographs, miscellaneous part I, 1978-1980 (Box 68, Folder 10)
  - Photographs, 1976-1980 (Box 68, Folder 11)
  - Negatives, circa 1970s-1980s (Box 68, Folder 12)
  - Appointment book, 1975 (Box 69)
  - Appointment book, 1976 (Box 69)
  - Appointment book, 1977 (Box 69)
  - Appointment book, 1978 (Box 70)
  - Appointment book, 1979 (Box 70)
  - Appointment book, 1980 (Box 70)
  - Small appointment books, passports, 1970s-1980s (Box 71)
  - Campaign contributors (Box 72)
  - Issues: Abortion, 1974-1981 (Box 73, Folder 1)
  - Issues: Amnesty, March 12, 1974 (Box 73, Folder 2)
  - Issues: Campaign reform, 1974 (Box 73, Folder 3)
  - Issues: Civil service, 1972-1974 (Box 73, Folder 4)
  - Issues: Constituent service, 1974 (Box 73, Folder 5)
  - Issues: Criminal justice, 1974 (Box 73, Folder 6)
  - Issues: Culture, May 4, 1974 (Box 73, Folder 7)
  - Issues: Defence, 1973-1974 (Box 73, Folder 8)
  - Issues: District of Columbia, December 17, 1973 (Box 73, Folder 9)
  - Issues: Education elementary and secondary, 1974 (Box 73, Folder 10)
  - Issues: Education, higher, 1974 (Box 73, Folder 11)
  - Issues: Employment and manpower, 1974 (Box 73, Folder 12)